Hi, and that lesson I will do a quick overview of Coresore AI.
Coresore AI is a smart code editor that's getting really a lot of attention.
It's not just another text editor like Visual Studio Code, it's a coding AI assistant
that help you work faster and smarter.
It can help you write code easier with less effort allowing you focus on your energy on
the problem-solving and collaboration.
What is Coresore AI is built on?
It was built, of course, on the top of Visual Studio Code editor, but supercharged with
AI.
It understands your code, suggests improvements, write code for you and connects to top
models like GPT4, Claude, Gamingy, and much others.
So Coresore was created by X, Open AI, and Google engineers, the goal was to help developers
easily use AI in the according workflow.
Now, let's talk what features suggest Coresore, because they designed it a lot of features
to enhance your coding experience and productivity, and let's go through it.
So, the first feature is the code out of completion.
Coresore suggests edits around your Coresore, not just insertions or additional code, so
where you put your Coresore, it can do some suggestions, and also it can suggest in some
other places of your file, because it's analyzing what can be improved.
It can do some suggestions based on your recent changes and linear errors.
It can also modify a multiple lines at once.
There is a nice features agent, agent is a Coresore AI assistance that lives in your
sidebar, in chat.
So, you can ask multiple questions about unfamiliar code, get some explanation, or explore
your code base.
You can make some small tweaks, or even large multi-file changes without manually navigating
the files.
You can get terminal command suggestions for your specific use case.
So, here we just look through some general feature explanation, and in the next lesson I will
go through in details with most popular use cases you can use the Coresore AI.
So, it has also an online edit feature, which allows you to generate new code or existing
code directly in the digital window.
You can generate a new code base in your prompt, or you can select code, and ask some
quick questions you can ask, can you improve this part of code, or suggest some fixes,
so improve the performance.
So, now the stock work or store is available.
It's available in most of operation systems like resource to get code, like a Mac, Windows,
and Linux.
So, you can use Coresore, doesn't matter what operation system you use.
I hope this quick overview was useful for you and see you in the next lesson.
[BLANK_AUDIO]